### **Finlay Craig**

294 Burnfield Road, Glasgow finlaycraig96@googlemail.com 07898111358 https://www.linkedin.com/in/finlaycraig/

Good Afternoon,

I appreciate you taking the time to consider my application, I read about this position online, and thought that the role suited me perfectly.

Extremely driven, hard working and well organised Computing Graduate, seeking a challenging and rewarding work environment, which will allow me to progress in my chosen career as a Graphic Designer.

With many years experience of graphic design, web design and marketing, SEO and administration experience, having designed graphics, flyers, logos and emails, creating websites, videos and animations. Running sales campaigns and event organising.

I have proven myself as a fast and enthusiastic learner with good organisational skills and my previous work experience proves my adaptability and excellent rapport with others.

I look forward to hearing from you in the near future.

Sincerely,

Finlay Craig

Click here! finlays-portfolio.com

## FINLAY CRAIG



finlaycraig96@googlemail.com 07898111358 294 Burnfield Road, Glasgow

#### Skills

Photoshop • Web Design Indesign • Adobe Premiere After Effects • Magento Microsoft Office • CSS • GA Html • Illustrator • Figma JavaScript • Wordpress Zapier • SetMore • Magento

#### **Experience**

Design
Marketing
Web Design
Digital Art
Video Editing
Teamwork
Administration

#### Personality

Creative • Intuitive • Friendly Organised • Team Player Resourceful • Dedicated Great Under Pressure Good General Knowledge Attention To Detail

#### **Equipment**

Powerful Desktop PC DSLR Camera Wacom Intuos Tablet Laptop Dacia Sandero

A Good Attitude

Education

(2:1) BSc Hons Computing: Graphics and Animation Robert Gordon University Sept 2014 - Jul 2018

HNC in Computing North East Scotland College Sept 2013 – Jul 2014

Advanced Excel Training Solab IT Services May 2019

#### **Employment**

Graphic Designer ROX - Diamonds & Thrills Luxury Jewellery and Watch Retailer January 2021 - Present

> Freelance Design Work January 2015 - Present

Marketing Assistant Dingbro Ltd.

Car Component Distributor April 2019 - September 2021

Workshop Technician North East Telecomms Radio Equipment Company August 2018 – April 2019

Administrator Craig, Allan & Co. Law Consultancy May 2014 – August 2018

Click here! finlays-portfolio.com



finlaycraig96@googlemail.com 07898111358 294 Burnfield Road, Glasgow

## Graphic Designer ROX - Diamonds & Thrills January 2022 - Present

Designing graphics and editing videos for social media accounts. Overseeing social content, liaising with external brands to meet campaign deadlines. Creative lead on the annual magazine, developing the brand's look.

Working with the sales team to update the website, design marketing emails and window displays regarding current offers and new products. Creating emails and invitations, helping to organise events and RVSP lists.

SEO and design updates for the company websites, deploying HTML and CSS, using Wordpress and Magento workspaces.

### Freelance Design Work January 2015 - Present

Creating and designing on projects for clients, adapting to suit their needs and briefs. These projects include; Logos, Animations, Web Design, Banners, T-Shirts, Flyers, Posters, Video Editing & Tattoos.

# Marketing Assistant Dingbro Ltd April 2019 - September 2021

Creating flyers for sale staff, creating a fresh professional brand identity to help promote the business overseeing magazine content and maintaining product pricing.

Administration for the online sales portal Allicat Online.

Click here! finlays-portfolio.com